<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!DOCTYPE ONIXmessage SYSTEM "http://www.editeur.org/onix/2.1/short/onix-international.dtd" ><ONIXmessage><header><m174>B&amp;H Publishing</m174><m175>Catherine Toolan 978-465-7755</m175><m283>eloquence@firebrandtech.com</m283><m182>20120202</m182><m184>eng</m184><m185>01</m185><m186>USD</m186><m187>in</m187></header><product><a001>1001-6970428</a001><a002>03</a002><productidentifier><b221>02</b221><b244>1433672448</b244></productidentifier><productidentifier><b221>03</b221><b244>9781433672446</b244></productidentifier><productidentifier><b221>15</b221><b244>9781433672446</b244></productidentifier><b012>DG</b012><b014>EPUB</b014><productclassification><b274>07</b274><b275>A_EGOODS_DIGITALBOOKS</b275></productclassification><b211>029</b211><b213>Open Ebook Format</b213><b214>06</b214><n338/><title><b202>01</b202><b203>American Heroes: In the Fight Against Radical Islam</b203></title><workidentifier><b201>15</b201><b244>9781433672446</b244></workidentifier><contributor><b034>1</b034><b035>A01</b035><b036>Oliver North</b036><b037>North, Oliver</b037><b039>Oliver</b039><b040>North</b040><b044><![CDATA[<DIV><FONT><b>Oliver North</b> is a combat-decorated Marine, the  recipient of the Silver Star, the Bronze Star for valor, and two Purple  Hearts for wounds in action. From 1983 to 1986 he served as the U.S.  government&rsquo;s counter-terrorism coordinator on the National Security  Council staff. President Ronald Reagan described him as &ldquo;an American  hero.&rdquo; A <i>New York Times</i> best-selling author, syndicated columnist, and host of the award-winning <i>War Stories</i>  documentary series on the FOX News Channel, North lives with his wife,  Betsy, in Virginia. They have four children and twelve grandchildren.<BR></div>]]></b044></contributor><contributor><b034>2</b034><b035>B01</b035><b036>Chuck Holton</b036><b037>Holton, Chuck</b037><b039>Chuck</b039><b040>Holton</b040><b044><![CDATA[<DIV><FONT><P><B>Chuck Holton</B> spent four years with the 75th Ranger Regiment, flew military helicopters and now travels the world as the &quot;adventure Correspondent&quot; for CBN. He is the author of five books, including the Task Force Valor Series, <i>A More Elite Soldier,</i> and <i>Bulletproof: The Making of an Invincible Mind</i>. He splits his time between his home in Panama and his farm in Appalachia, where he enjoys raising animals with his wife and five children.</p></div>]]></b044></contributor><b049>by Oliver North</b049><n386/><language><b253>01</b253><b252>eng</b252></language><b061>304</b061><b062>375 color</b062><b064>HIS027170</b064><audience><b204>01</b204><b206>01</b206></audience><othertext><d102>13</d102><d103>02</d103><d104><![CDATA[<DIV><FONT><DIV><B><P>Oliver North </B>is a Vietnam veteran awarded the Silver Star, Bronze Star, and two Purple Hearts during his twenty-two years of service as a U.S. Marine. He was later assigned to the National Security Council staff by former President Ronald Reagan, who called North &#8220;an American hero.&#8221; Today, he is a best-selling author, syndicated columnist, and host of the award-winning <I>War Stories </I>series on the FOX News Channel. North has four children, eight grandchildren, and lives with his wife in Virginia.</P><B><P>Chuck Holton </B>is a U.S. military veteran and now travels the world as Adventure Correspondent for the Christian Broadcasting Network (CBN).</P></DIV></DIV>]]></d104></othertext><othertext><d102>01</d102><d103>02</d103><d104><![CDATA[<DIV><FONT><DIV><P>A <I>New York Times, Wall Street Journal, </I>and <I>Washington Post </I>best seller, now available with a new chapter on events in Afghanistan plus an exclusive online&#160;access&#160;code for three downloadable episodes of <I>War Stories</I>!</P><P>What is a hero? Oliver North says, &#8220;Real heroes are selfless. Those who serve America in harm&#8217;s way in the war against radical Islam have that quality in abundance. And so do their families and loved ones at home. Yet, they rarely get the attention or coverage they deserve . . . I never cease to be amazed at the self-discipline of these brave young Americans. They can endure the adrenaline-pumping violence of enemy engagement, and then, just minutes later, help school children get safely to their classes . . . No nation&#8212;ours included&#8212;has ever had a military force better than the one we have today.&#8221;</P><P>In <I>American Heroes</I>, North offers an inspiring, first-hand account of the extraordinary men and women defending America against radical Islamic terror from his perspective as a forty year member of the United States military, a member of the National Security Council staff and serving as the U.S. counter-terrorism coordinator from 1983-1986. This patriotic book also pulls in the very latest reports and exclusive full-color photographs from War Stories, the award-winning FOX News Channel series hosted by North.</P></DIV></DIV>]]></d104></othertext><othertext><d102>02</d102><d103>02</d103><d104><![CDATA[<DIV><FONT><DIV><P>Oliver North writes firsthand accounts of faithful American heroes in the fight against global terrorism and jihad; a <I>New York Times </I>best seller now in trade paper with updated chapter on Afghanistan plus a code for two downloadable episodes of <I>War Stories</I>.</P></DIV></DIV>]]></d104></othertext><imprint><b241>02</b241><b242>Firebrand Cloud Imprint Key</b242><b243>4028337</b243><b079>Fidelis</b079></imprint><publisher><b291>01</b291><b241>01</b241><b242>Firebrand Cloud Publisher Key</b242><b243>4028289</b243><b081>B&amp;H Publishing Group</b081></publisher><b394>04</b394><b003>20090501</b003><salesrights><b089>02</b089><b388>WORLD</b388></salesrights><measure><c093>08</c093><c094>0</c094><c095>lb</c095></measure><relatedproduct><h208>13</h208><productidentifier><b221>15</b221><b244>9780805449532</b244></productidentifier></relatedproduct><supplydetail><j137>ReThink Books</j137><j268>02</j268><j269>Y</j269><j141>IP</j141><j396>20</j396><j143>20090501</j143><price><j148>01</j148><j149>0040</j149><discountcoded><j363>02</j363><j364>0040</j364></discountcoded><j151>24.99</j151><j152>USD</j152></price></supplydetail></product></ONIXmessage>
